{
    "1": [
        {
            "question": "1",
            "response": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "2",
            "response": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "3",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "4",
            "response": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "5",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "1",
            "response": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "2",
            "response": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "3",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "4",
            "response": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "5",
            "response": "A"
        }
    ],
    "2": [
        {
            "question": "1",
            "response": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "2",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "3",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "4",
            "response": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "5",
            "response": "A"
        }
    ],
    "3": [
        {
            "question": "1",
            "response": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "2",
            "response": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "3",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "4",
            "response": "D"
        },
        {
            "question": "5",
            "response": "B"
        }
    ],
    "4": [
        {
            "question": "1",
            "response": "A"
        },
        {
            "question": "2",
            "response": "C"
        },
        {
            "question": "3",
            "response": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "4",
            "response": "B"
        },
        {
            "question": "5",
            "response": "A"
        }
    ]
}